https://www.ijpr.org/privacy-terms-of-use

Play Live Radio
Next Up:
Privacy / Terms of Use
Jefferson Public Radio (JPR) and the JPR Foundation (JPRF) maintain an ongoing commitment to the values of integrity, honesty, transparency and responsibility with its listeners, constituents and stakeholders. Toward achieving this goal, JPR and the JPRF outline the following Privacy Policy and Terms of Use for this website.PRIVACY POLICYProtecting your privacy begins with a complete understanding of what information can be collected from you and how that information is used. Should you have any questions regarding your privacy and our policy after reading this document, please contact JPR for clarification at: jprinfo@sou.edu or call us during business hours at 541-552-6301.YOUR MEMBERSHIP INFORMATIONUpon your request, the JPRF will provide you with the current information (e.g., name, address, email, etc.) that we maintain about you through the most secure means available. Names, email addresses, telephone numbers, mailing addresses or other personal membership information will not be sold or traded to any other party.
FINANCIAL SECURITYJPR and the JPRF make every effort to ensure that all of the transactions that occur on its website are secure. All credit card numbers submitted to the site are encrypted, which is the industry standard for information security. In the unlikely event that the information you send is intercepted, it is nearly impossible to decrypt the information. Your peace of mind and security is very important to us. If you do not feel comfortable submitting your personal information online, you can make a contribution to support JPR by calling at 541-552-6301.
INFORMATION GATHERED AND HOW WE USE ITAll web servers generate log files that record basic information about website "traffic" - what files or "pages" are requested, when they are requested, how many requests were made, what browser requested it, etc. These logs serve to help us understand how successful our site is in serving you. These logs do not collect personal information about you and are only reviewed to create an aggregate demographic profile of our site users. Visitors to this website may voluntarily supply personal information for the purpose of entering contests, sending email, signing up for email newsletters, commenting on stories, participating in social media networks, making e-commerce transactions and responding to surveys or polls. JPR and the JPRF may use this information for its own internal use solely to conduct the stated activities. We reserve the right to send you email relating to your account status. This includes order confirmations, renewal/expiration notices, communication about credit card problems, other transactional emails and notifications about major changes to our website. If you have registered for online discussions or other services, you may receive email specific to your participation in those activities. If you no longer wish to receive email communication from us, you may opt out by following the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of any email we send you.LINKS TO OTHER SITESThis website may contain links to other third party sites that may not follow the same privacy policies as ijpr.org. These sites may use cookies, collect data, and use the data in ways that JPR and the JPRF would not. JPR and the JPRF are not responsible for the privacy practices or any information or materials on these other sites.ACCEPTANCE OF THIS POLICYBy using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of this website following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. Updated: August 15, 2013
TERMS OF USEThank you for using ijpr.org, a public service of Southern Oregon University, the JPR Foundation and part of the NPR Digital Network. The following terms of use apply to all users of this site.
ACCEPTANCE OF TERMSBy accessing this website you accept and agree to be bound, without limitation or qualification, by these Terms. If you do not accept any of the terms and conditions of this Agreement, please do not use the website. JPR may, in its sole discretion, modify or revise the Terms at any time by updating this Web page. You are bound by any such modification and should therefore visit this page periodically to review the Terms.COPYRIGHT INFORMATIONThe contents of this website, including but not limited to text, software, photographs, graphics, audio, video, logos, trademarks, service marks and other material ("Material") are protected by copyright and other laws in both the United States and international law. The Material includes content owned or controlled by JPR or the JPRF and content owned or controlled by third parties and licensed to JPR/JPRF. Unless expressly authorized by this Agreement, you must obtain prior written permission from JPR/JPRF before using the Material.USE OF CONTENTYou may view and download a single copy of the Material on the website solely for your personal and non-commercial use. You may not sell or modify the Material or reproduce, display, distribute, or otherwise use the Material in any way for any public or commercial purpose without the express written permission of JPR/JPRF. All requests for uses beyond personal and non-commercial use should be referred to jprinfo@sou.edu.RESTRICTION OF USEYou may use this website only in a lawful manner and for lawful purposes and consistent with this Agreement. You may not use this website in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the site or interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of the site. You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to this website, other accounts, computer systems or networks connected to ijpr.org, through hacking, password mining or any other means. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available through the JPR website.ONLINE COMMUNICATIONSYou are cautioned that any online communications may not be fully confidential. In addition, you should be aware that federal postal regulations do not protect electronic mail. You should be aware that some administrative personnel of JPR or the JPRF may, in the course of their regular duties, have access to communications for technical or operational purposes. JPR/JPRF may also disclose any communications to the extent permitted or required by law.WARRANTY DISCLAIMERThis website is provided "As Is" without warranties of any kind, either express or implied, including without limitation warranties of title, non-infringement, or implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose and your use of the website is at your own risk. If you are dissatisfied with any of the Materials or other contents of the website or with the Terms, Privacy Policy, or other policies, your sole remedy is to discontinue use of the website. Any downloading of software or other materials or any other use of the Information on the website is at your risk, and you are advised to take adequate precautions to minimize any loss to your system, including use of anti-virus programs and proper backup of files. Further, JPR/JPRF does not warrant that any information is complete or accurate, that the website will be error free or that any information provided is free of malicious programming.LIMITATION OF LIABILITYIN NO EVENT SHALL JPR, THE JPRF OR SOUTHERN OREGON UNIVERSITY BE LIABLE TO ANY USER OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY OR LOST PROFITS) RESULTING FROM THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEBSITE OR THE MATERIAL, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT JPR/JPRF IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.RELEASE AND INDEMNITYYOU HEREBY RELEASE AND WAIVE ANY AND ALL CLAIMS AND/OR LIABILITY AGAINST JPR, THE JPRF AND SOUTHERN OREGON UNIVERSITY ARISING FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE. YOU ALSO AGREE TO DEFEND, INDEMNIFY AND HOLD HARMLESS, JPR, THE JPRF AND SOUTHERN OREGON UNIVERSITY FROM AND AGAINST, ANY AND ALL CLAIMS OR LIABILITY, INCLUDING COSTS AND ATTORNEYS FEES, ARISING FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE OR FAILURE TO ABIDE BY APPLICABLE LAW.LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITESThis website may contain hyperlinks to websites operated by parties other than JPR/JPRF. Such hyperlinks are provided for your reference only. Neither JPR or JPRF control such websites and therefore are not responsible for their contents. Inclusion of hyperlinks to such websites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such websites or any association with their operators.MISCELLANEOUSThese terms will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Oregon. You consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the courts of the Oregon, United States in case of any dispute connected with this site or the Terms. If any of these terms and conditions is found unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision will be considered severable from the remaining terms and conditions, and will not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions. This is the entire agreement between you, JPR and the JPRF relating to the subject matter it contains. This agreement may be modified at any time by JPR or JPRF by posting changes to these Terms of Use.Updated: August 15, 2013
